Jai Shri Krishna friends, we know that
these days new diseases have increased a lot and
even young children and young people can get this disease very
easily. In such a situation, a
very good plan in which you get a sum assured
along with Mediclave for these particular diseases and
for that you
get a sum assured and you get those expenses
from the company. So let's get some information about it.
This plan is called Comprehensive Critical Illness which covers 92 critical illnesses.
92 critical illnesses are covered in it. In it,
whatever illness we get, the
expenses we incur due to it.
We get money according to the sum assured. There are two parts in it,
major critical and minor critical illness. If
major critical illness is the last stage
or something like that, then you get 100% of the sum
assured.
And if it is minor i.e.
first stage then you get 25% of the sum assured
cost.
Which illnesses are covered then cancer and
blood disorder related major and minor four
and one heart and blood vessel related
major 10 and minor 11 major organ
related major 10 14 and minor 12
nervous system related which is major 24
illnesses are covered and minor eight and
apart from that burn in other illnesses all those are covered in
which major has three and
minor five so making a total of 55 major and
37 minor illnesses are covered in this and a total of
92 are covered. If we look at the premium of this through an example then
any person takes a
sum assured cover of 5 lakhs 10 lakhs or 25 lakhs
then if he is a person of 21 to 25
years of age then he will have to pay
from 1565 rupees  3131 and
7826 for 25 lakhs, in the same way, for 26 to 30, 31
to 35, 36 to 40, 41 to 45, 46 to 50 and
51 to 55, how much is the premium of 5
lakhs, 10 lakhs and 25 lakhs in a period of five years.
Here we have
given special care that if
you have taken a mediclaim, are you admitted, are you undergoing treatment, then you will
get the bill there. If
you have taken this plan, then
you will get 100% fixed amount of sum assured
for treatment and if there is a minor
relaxation, then you will get 25% of sum assured.
The condition is the same that a normal healthy person,
that is, he should not have any of these diseases already, he should be a
physically fit normal
healthy person and once again
only what the doctor says.  If
we take this plan and submit the copy of the paper to the medical office,
we get a fixed amount, then along with the details of this plan,
I will list the 92 critical illness covers
and the premiums. In this too, if
you are looking for a cover of more than 25 lakhs, you are
eligible to get it
and if it is a very nominal amount, then
I will share the details with you. Thank you. In
addition, there is a very nice feature in this that
suppose that once we get cancer
detected and 100% or 25% of the time we take money
according to which major or minor illness we have, then
you get the money for cancer,
but after that, if any other
disease occurs, heart related or organ related
or nervous system related, then
your policy will continue. As long as you
pay the premium,
your policy will continue for these other illnesses
and you will also be eligible to get it, so that is also a
very nice idea.  Thank you.